欢迎回来。
Welcome back.
现在让我们快速了解 HTML 到底是什么
Let's now very quickly learn what HTML actually is
以及我们可以用它做什么。
and what we can do with it.
所以基本上 HTML 代表超文本标记语言和
So basically HTML stands for Hypertext Markup language and
还记得我们之前是如何了解到 HTML 是
remembered how we learned earlier that HTML is one of the
核心网络技术以及 CSS 和 JavaScript。
core web technologies along with CSS and JavaScript.
现在，
Right, now,
HTML 是一种标记语言，我们的 Web 开发人员可以使用它
HTML is a markup language that we web developers can use to
结构和描述任何网页的全部内容。
structure and describe the entire content of any webpage.
所以请注意我所说的标记语言，
So notice how I said markup language,
因为 HTML 真的不是一种编程语言。
because HTML is really not a programming language.
它是一种标记语言，因为我们使用它
It's a markup language because we use it
形容某事。
to describe something.
在 HTML 的情况下，
And in the case of HTML,
我们确实使用元素来描述内容。
we do describe content using elements.
所以我们有不同的元素可以用来描述
So we have different elements that we can use to describe
不同类型的内容。例如，
different types of content. So for example,
我们有我们在讲座中已经使用过的 P 元素
we have the P element that we already used in the lecture
我们在那里创建了我们的第一个网页。
where we created our very first webpage.
所以我们在那里使用 P 元素来创建一个段落，
And so we use the P element there to create a paragraph,
但我们真的有各种不同的元素。
but we really have all kinds of different elements.
所以创建链接的元素，创建页面标题，
So elements to create links, to create page headings,
图片、视频等等，
images, video, and a lot more,
正如您将在本节中学习的那样。
as you will learn throughout this section.
基本上贯穿整个课程，
And basically throughout the entire course,
然后，正如我们在那堂课中学到的那样
then, as we also learned in that lecture
我们在那里建立了我们的第一个网页，
where we built our very first webpage,
网络浏览器，例如谷歌浏览器，
web browsers, such as Google Chrome,
基本上理解 HTML 代码并可以渲染它
do essentially understand HTML code and can render it
作为最终网站，所以我们可以看到的网站
as a final website, so website that we can see
在浏览器中。
in the browser.
好的。
Okay.
所以这本质上就是 HTML 和
So this is essentially what HTML is and
我们可以用它做什么。
what we can do with it.
但是现在让我们稍微放大一下看看
But now let's just zoom in a little bit and take a look at
HTML 元素的剖析。
the anatomy of a HTML element.
所以基本上看一下构建块
So basically take a look at the building blocks of
每个 HTML 元素。
each HTML element.
再一次，我们在这里查看段落元素，
And again, we are looking at the paragraph element here,
正如你所看到的那样。
as you can see by the P.
所以这里的所有这些实际上都是元素本身。
And so all of this here is actually the element itself.
现在一个 HTML 元素通常由三部分组成。
Now an HTML element is usually made up of three parts.
首先是开始标签，它是元素的名称。
First is the opening tag, which is the name of the element.
所以在这种情况下，
So in this case,
它是包裹在小于中的P而不是在更大的巢穴中
it's the P wrapped in the less than in the greater den
符号，可能它们还有其他名称，
symbols, probably they have some other names,
但这就是我喜欢称呼这些符号的方式。
but that's how I like to call the symbols.
所以它小于 P 然后大于。
So it's less than P and then greater than.
然后，在那之后，
Then, after that,
我们基本上有了元素的内容。
we have basically the content of the element.
所以在这个例子中，这只是文本，
So in this example, that is just text,
但可能还有其他类型的内容。
but there might be other types of content.
例如，一个元素本身可以包含，
For example, an element can contain in itself,
另一个元素，我们称之为子元素。
another element which we then call a child element.
还有一些元素，比如图像，实际上已经
Also some elements such as images have actually
根本没有内容，只有开放技术。
no content at all and have only an opening tech.
而这一切当然会变成
And all of this will of course become
在我们开始编写 HTML 时非常直观。
very intuitive as we start writing HTML.
就是这样，
This is just so that,
当我谈到开始标签时，你知道我在说什么
you know what I'm talking about when I speak of opening tag
或结束标签或内容，并谈到结束标签，
or closing tag or content, and speaking of the closing tag,
它与开始标签基本相同，
it is basically the same as the opening tag,
但有一个斜线。
but with a slash.
所以它只是用 P 打开它的段落元素
So it opens its paragraph element simply with the P
然后我们用斜线 P 关闭它，好的。
and we then close it with slash P, okay.
现在对于没有的元素内容
Now for elements that do not have content
比如我之前提到的图像元素，
such as the image element that I mentioned before,
我们实际上省略了结束标签。 所以在那种情况下，
we actually omit the closing tag. So in that case,
我们只有开始标签，仅此而已，
we only have the opening tag and that's it,
我们当然会看到这一点
and we will see that in action of course
一旦我们开始将图像集成到网页中。
once we start integrating images into a webpage.
好的，那是真的，
Okay, and that's really,
开始学习 HTML 和练习所需的一切，
all you need in order to start learning HTML and practice,
这正是我们在下一节课中要做的。
which is exactly what we will do in the next lecture.